Contact

01402711407 (Mobile) monjurulahshan01@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/m0njurul (LinkedIn) m0njurul.me/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills
Web Design
Security Researcher

Cybersecurity

Md. Monjurul Ahshan Rahat

CTF Player & Bug Bounty Hunter | Ethical Hacker Dhaka, Bangladesh

Summary

I am Md. Monjurul Ahshan Rahat. I am a student of Computer Engineering. I do Bug Bounty Hunting and occasionally I participate in CTF / Cyber drill competitions.

I have been learning and working on Security Research for over 2 years with high interest in Cyber Security.

Experience

Bugcrowd Researcher December 2019 - Present (2 years 10 months)

Sec Miner's Bangladesh - Cyber Security Researchers Security Researcher December 2020 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Education

Ahsanullah Institute of Technical & Vocational Education & Training Diploma , Computer Science · (2020 - 2024)

A.K. High School and College Secondary School Certificate, Business/Commerce, General · (2015 - 2020)

Haidar Ali School and College Primary Education Completion (2009 - 2014)